[{
        "question": "Where is Rome?",
        "correctAnswer": "Italy",
        "wrongAnswers": ["France", "USA", "Poland"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Garfields favorite food?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lasagne",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Spinach", "Pizza", "Pasta"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Australia",
        "correctAnswer": "Canberra",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Brisbane"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which currency is used for money transactions in Japan?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yen",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Dollar", "Euro", "Pound"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first president of the United States of America?",
        "correctAnswer": "George Washington",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Thomas Jefferson", "Abraham Lincoln", "Theodore Roosevelt"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was not a member of the rock band Rolling Stones?",
        "correctAnswer": "David Bowie",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Mick Jagger", "Keith Richards", "Charlie Watts"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson Mandela was South African's first black president during...?",
        "correctAnswer": "1994 - 1999",
        "wrongAnswers": ["1990 - 1994", "1985 - 1990", "1999 - 2003"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The famous Tower Bridge can be found in which city?",
        "correctAnswer": "London",
        "wrongAnswers": ["San Francisco", "Paris", "Venice"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Albert Einstein, who developed the theory of relativity was born in...?",
        "correctAnswer": "Germany",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Austria", "Switzerland", "Netherlands"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which famous singer died in June 2009?",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Whitney Houston", "Amy Winehouse", "David Bowie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Yellow Submarine is a song from 1966 by which band?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
        "wrongAnswers": ["The Rolling Stones", "The Beach Boys", "Bee Gees"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Nobel Prize was named after the Swedish chemist …?",
        "correctAnswer": "Alfred Nobel",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Alfons Nobel", "Albert Nobel", "Alex Nobel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which region of Italy you find the leaning tower of Pisa?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tuscany",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Sardinia", "Calabria", "Lombardy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caracas is the capital of …?",
        "correctAnswer": "Venezuela",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Paraguay", "Uruguay", "Bolivia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year the online video sharing plattform Youtube was created?",
        "correctAnswer": "2005",
        "wrongAnswers": ["2007", "2009", "2011"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the text of the first SMS message?",
        "correctAnswer": "Merry Christmas",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Happy Birthday", "Hello World", "How are you"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The famous Tower Bridge is a world-famour symbol of what city?",
        "correctAnswer": "London",
        "wrongAnswers": ["San Francisco", "Paris", "Venice"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the chemical element with the symbol Au?",
        "correctAnswer": "gold",
        "wrongAnswers": ["silver", "nickel", "platinum"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A human has seven cervical vertebrae. Ho many does a giraffe have?",
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "wrongAnswers": ["17", "27", "37"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrew Lloyd Webber is one of the most famous composer of musical theatre. Which musical is not composed by Andrew Lloyd Webber? ",
        "correctAnswer": "Elisabeth",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Evita", "Cats", "The Phantom of the Opera"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Ballon d'Or is an annual football award. Who won with six awards the most Ballon d'Or in history?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lionel Messi",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ronaldo", "Franz Beckenbauer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wlliam Shakespeare's play Much Ado About Nothing was filmed in 1993. Who is not playing in that movie?",
        "correctAnswer": "Julia Roberts",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Denzel Wahsington", "Keanu Reeves", "Emma Thompson"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which planet is the smallest and innermost planet in the Solar System?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mercury",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Venus", "Earth", "Mars"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The magnetized needle of a compass is always pointing to the ...?",
        "correctAnswer": "North",
        "wrongAnswers": ["South", "West", "East"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The American online social media and social networking service Facebook was launched in …?",
        "correctAnswer": "2004",
        "wrongAnswers": ["2002", "2000", "2006"]
    },
    {
        "question": "London has several of England's leading football clubs. Which is none of them?",
        "correctAnswer": "Manchester United",
        "wrongAnswers": ["Arsenal", "Chelsea", "West Ham United"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hobbit is a bestseller by the autor  …?",
        "correctAnswer": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
        "wrongAnswers": ["J.K.Rowling", "Dan Brown", "Antoine de Saint-Exupery"]
    }
]